Something like this...
こんな感じで...
Are you going to record this on video?
これビデオで撮るんですか?
Yes, I always do videos.
そう、俺はいつもビデオ
Let's take pictures, have a photo session, etc.
撮るっしょ、撮影会とか
Well, most of the pictures are taken with a camera.
まあ、でもほとんどカメラで撮る
Ah, but I can take a photo of this.
ああ、でもこれ写真撮れる
Take a nice photo and snap a photo.
いいショットで写真カシャっと撮って
If you don't want to show your face too much in the video,
ビデオであまり顔とか映さないといけば、
Just the body...
体だけ...
It's not showing.
映ってないんで
The atmosphere is nice, isn't it?
ちょっと雰囲気はいいでしょ?
It's the atmosphere.
雰囲気ですよ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
Can you see it a little?
ちょっと映ってる?
I like your great style.
すごいスタイルいいね
A little help...
ちょっと手...
Is that okay then?
じゃあいいですか?
I guess it makes me stiff.
凝りされるとか
Didn't you take an image video?
イメージビデオで撮っとってない?
Image videos...
イメージビデオとか...
what do you want?
なんでしょう?
Well, it's kind of like that...
まあ、なんかそのちょっと...
Something...
なんかさ...
Cosplay...
コスプレがさ...
I saw it earlier, but it's not there, right?
さっき見たけど、ないんじゃない?
This button.
このボタン
Was there no cosplay?
コスプレなかったんですか?
Well, just the outfit.
まあ、その服装だけ
got it.
わかりました
Can I have you stand for a moment?
じゃあちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
Is this okay?
これ大丈夫ですか?
It's amazing.
すげーいいよ
Uncle or something...
おじとか...
Is it quite a bit lower?
結構ちょっと下は?
Down.
下ね
Like clothes that are revealing blue.
露出が青いもんの服とかね
It has a face on it.
顔ついてますね
Can I follow you too much?
あ んまりついていいですか?
I don't have much trouble with it.
あんまりついて困ってない
Well, something like that...
まあ、そのなんか...
It's a hobby.
趣味なんで
This is the only thing I see.
これしか見ない
Still, it would be bad if I gave it to someone else.
それでも外にもらえたらまずいので
Let's take a look at some hobbies.
ちょっと趣味を見ます
As I said earlier, it's a little...
さっきも言ったけど、ちょっと...
Swimsuit?
水着?
Are swimsuits okay?
水着とか大丈夫?
If it's a swimsuit...
水着だったら...
Do you want to photograph something like that?
そう いう何か撮りたいの?
I don't have any cosplay, so I don't have time.
コスプレないからさ、時間もあれだから
It looks like a swimsuit, right?
水着みたいなでしょ?
What about swimwear?
水着は?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
underwear?
下着?
It's like a swimsuit.
水着みたいなもんじゃん
No, underwear and swimsuits are different.
いや、下着とか水着は違う
Isn't the underwear a little bad?
下着はちょっと良くない?
What about underwear?
下着は?
Underwear is not allowed.
下 着 は ダ メです
Cover it a little?
ちょっと 被る?
People are more likely to wear something.
人の方がなんか被る
With humanity.
人情で
Is it interesting?
面白いですか?
Hey, it's just underwear.
ちょっとさ、下着ですよ
I just don't like it.
なんかちょっと嫌ですよ
It's a secret.
内緒です
It's a little early.
ちょっと早いです
It's above.
上です
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Isn't that an assage?
アッサージじゃないですか
It's above.
上です
It's pretty but soft.
結構でも柔らかいね
I feel like it went up properly.
ちゃんと上がった気がする
Well then, can I judge the swimsuit?
じゃあさ、水着審査していいですか?
You want to wear a swimsuit.
水着したいですよね
Think of it as a swimsuit.
水着だと思ってね
You're used to it now, right?
今度慣れてるでしょ?
I thought it was a swimsuit.
水着だと思って
We're together.
一緒じゃん
Thin legs.
足細い
It's thin.
細いね
Hey.
ねぇ
You're on time, aren't you?
間に合ってるんだよね
After all, sneak into the hole.
やっぱ穴にこっそり
No, that's terrible.
いや、ひどいな
That's terrible, don't go near it.
ひどいね、近づかない
Look behind you.
後ろ見て
Wow!
うわ!
Let's take pictures of pets posing.
ペットでポーズみたいなの撮ろう
Pose?
ポーズ?
What kind of pose is good?
どんなポーズはいいですか?
Put your hands together like this.
両手をこう
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
sexy.
セクシー
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
What should I do?
どうしようとしちゃったら
Is it okay?
いい の?
Laugh out loud.
爆笑して
That's good.
いいっすね
Good.
いいっす
amazing.
すごい
Not much of a face...
あんまり顔は...
It's not on.
ついてないよ
ついてないっすね
A little foot.
ちょっと足
Have it stand like this.
こう立ててもらう
The M word.
M字
Hands behind your back.
後ろに手って
Not much...
あんまり...
It's not on.
ついてないよ
Well, yeah.
まぁ、うん
Are you okay.
大丈夫
There's no face on it.
顔はついてない
Then I'll find something with balance.
そしたらなんかバランス付き出すやつ
You'll do it in gravure, right?
グラビアでやるでしょ
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
stomach
い
Let's meet.
ら っしゃいませ
Go to the back.
後ろへ行ってね
Try a massage.
マ ッサージしてみて
No change.
変わらない
Did you get a massage?
マ ッサージをしちゃったのか
Roll your butt too.
お尻も転がし
It's connected to my waist.
腰と繋がってるんだけど
Massage is fine.
マッサージ大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Something...
なんか...
I just want to see it.
ちょっとだけ見たいな
No.
ダメです
Well, a little.
まぁ、ちょっと
No.
ダメです
Well, kind of...
まぁ、なんか...
Wait, something...
ちょっと、なんか...
I don't really understand.
あんまりわかんない
What is it?
なんですか?
No.
ダメ
Hey, hey, just a little bit.
ちょ、ちょ、ちょっとだけ
Hey, take a break.
ちょ、ちょっと休みなさい
Hey, that.
ねぇ、あれ
That.
あれ
No.
ダメです
Well, I don't have enough strength.
体力つかないから、じゃあ
I won't have any physical strength from now on.
これからは体力つかないから
It's reflected.
映ってるです
It's reflected, isn't it?
映ってますよね
It's reflected.
映っちゃう
Please do not display it.
映さないようにしてください
It's really no good.
本当にダメです
Only I see
俺しか見ない
Really.
本当に
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Did you see it at all?
ちょっと見えた?
some time ago.
さっき
No.
ダメです
Please delete it.
消してください
All you have to do is turn it off.
消せばいいじゃん
No.
ダメです
Delete.
削除する
No.
ダメです
Look at it together later and delete it.
後で一緒に見て、削除する
That's fine, that's it.
いいじゃん、それ
I'll give you some money too.
お金もちょっとあげるし
No.
ダメです
Are you having fun taking photos?
楽しく撮ってないでいく?
Hey, really.
ちょっと、本当に
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Oh, look.
なんか、ほら
Style, you know.
スタイル、ほら
I guess I just want to take some nude photos.
ちょっとヌード撮りたいなっていうのあるじゃん
It was there.
せっかくあったし
I'll pay too.
お金も払うし
It would be bad if they found out.
バレたら、まずい
I won't find out, I won't find out.
バレない、バレない
You'll never find out.
絶対バレない
Because I don't know what's going on.
何があるかわかんないので
No.
ダメです
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと
ちょっと、 ちょっと
It's not shown here either.
ここも映ってない
It seriously doesn't show up.
マジで映ってない
I did it.
やった
It's seriously okay.
マジで大丈夫
Well, let's take a look, here.
じゃあ、見てみるじゃん、ほら
Look.
ほ ら
It doesn't show up, right?
映ってないでしょ
In this state,
この状態で、
Hey, it's okay.
ちょっと、 大丈夫
This is it, this is it.
これで、これで
But yes.
でも、はい
Isn't it over?
終わんない?
It won't end.
終わんない
Because it won't end.
終 わ ん ない から
You want it to end, right?
終わりたいでしょ
Well, it really ends.
あんま、本当に終わる
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
Wait, I shouldn't take pictures.
ちょっと、撮っちゃいけないじゃん
That's already dangerous.
それは、それはもう、危ないです
Isn't it okay to show me?
見せていいじゃない?
The face, the sound of the face.
顔、顔の音するわけですね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
So, just, uh, stand up.
じゃあ、ちょっと、えーっと、立って
Ah, that hurts.
あー、痛い
It's falling, it's falling.
落ちてる、落ちてる
I like it because it's invisible.
目に見えないから、 いいね
Come on, come on.
さあね、さあね
Okay, sideways again.
じゃあ、横、また
It happened like this.
こうなって
Eh, it's dazzling, isn't it?
えー、眩しいでしょ
No, just a little more, a little more.
いや、 もうちょい、もうちょい
I've shown you enough.
もう十分、見せました
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You're saying you don't like it.
嫌だって言ってるじゃん
Do you not like it?
嫌ですか?
I just can't help it.
ちょっと、しょうがない
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just a little bit, um, something, um.
ちょっとさ、あの、なんか、 あの、
What can I say, I just want to take pictures of Rude.
なんていうか、 ルードだけ撮りたい
No, I already took the picture.
いや、もう、もう、もう、撮った
I took a picture.
撮りました
Because I didn't take a picture.
撮ってないから
This is no good.
これじゃダメです
You took the picture, right?
撮ったじゃないですか
No, again.
いや、また
I didn't take any pictures.
撮 ってないもん
Wait a minute, then wait a minute.
ちょっと、じゃあ、ちょっと
No.
ダメ
good?
いい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Can't flow?
流せない?
I can't let it flow, so, uh, only my legs are open.
流せないから、 えーと、 足だけ開いてるじゃん
What do you think?
どうでしょ?
Just open your legs?
足だけ開いてみ?
I don't like that anymore.
もう、それも嫌です
I don't like it.
嫌です
Swimsuit.
水着
No.
ダメです
Wait, it doesn't feel right.
ちょっと、なんか、 ダメ
No.
ダメです
What do you think?
どうでしょ?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
If you didn't show your face, it didn't show up, right?
顔も映さないって、 映らなかったじゃないですか
It's not showing.
映してない
It's reflected.
映ってるじゃん
You can check it later and delete it.
後で確認して、 消せばいいじゃん
Do you really want to delete it?
本当に消しますか?
Yeah.
うん
I definitely have to erase it.
絶対消さないと
No, so check it after you're done.
いや、だから、 終わった後に確認しよ
It's fine when I'm doing it anyway.
とりあえずやってる時はいいし
Lost only my body.
体だけなくして
It's showing.
映してるじゃん
No, that's why, hey, hey,
いや、だから、 ちょっと、ちょっと、
Hey, I was just doing something.
ちょっと、したことしてんだって
It won't end.
終わらないって
Because it won't end.
終わらないから
It doesn't end.
終わりません
It never ends.
終わらない
still.
まだ
It won't end.
終われないよ
still.
まだ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Please stop your hands.
ちょっと、 手は、 手は、やめてください
I understand, I understand.
分かった、分かった
I don't touch it.
触ったりはしない
But no.
でもダメ
No.
ダメ
You're definitely trying to take pictures, aren't you?
絶対撮ろうとしてるじゃないですか
You can go home.
帰れますよ
Really.
本当に
You're saying you'll give me money.
お金渡すって言ってるでしょ
I didn't take pictures because my skin and face didn't look good.
撮らないって、肌顔がダメってやっちゃったじゃん
That's what I'm saying.
言ってるじゃん
You're saying no.
ダメって言ってるじゃん
I'm not saying that I have good skin.
肌顔がいいって言ってないです
Didn't I tell you that I only wore underwear?
下着だけだったらって話したじゃないですか
Don't even take pictures of your face.
顔も撮らないで
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
Give it back.
返せ
You get it.
分かるでしょ
it hurts?
痛い?
Please let me do it.
やらせてください
good.
いい
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
together.
一緒に
I don't like it.
嫌です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I don't like it.
嫌です
No, it's fine.
いや、いいじゃん
I've been taking pictures up to this point.
ここまで撮ってるんだから
Because I don't touch it.
触らないから
Sleep.
寝て
No.
ダメ
I don't like it.
嫌だって
嫌だ
Isn't this sleeping?
これ、寝てないの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってる
撮ってるよ
I didn't take a picture of my face.
顔は撮ってない
I'll erase it.
消すし
No.
ダメです
I was able to take some more pictures.
もうちょっと撮れたよ
No.
ダメ
I'm going home.
帰ります
Don't give me money.
お金渡すんねえよ
I'll contact you.
連絡しますよ
For the club.
クラブの方に
Want to take a little photo?
ちょっとだけ撮りたい?
No.
ダメです
I'll increase it a little.
ちょっと増やすし
If you make it a little thicker.
ちょっと分厚くすれば
Life is tough, isn't it?
生活大変でしょ?
That's true though.
そうですけど
But if you find out...
でも、バレたら...
I won't find out.
バレない
That won't be found out.
それは、バレない
Are you okay.
大丈夫
I won't find out.
バレない
Well, only I can see it.
だ って、俺しか見えないじゃん
Even if you saw it, you wouldn't see it.
見たとしては、見ないか
I don't see it.
見ない
Especially.
別に
Well, that's okay.
まあ、それは大丈夫
That's what it is.
そういうの
Now that it's over, let's talk.
終わったから、話そう
What should I do?
どうするか
For now, I'm the only one who can see it.
とりあえず、俺しか見えないから
But, you know, I'm also kind of a guy.
でも、ほら、俺もちょっと男だからさ
I'm a little excited.
ちょっと興奮しちゃってるから
If I don't see it, I can't go home.
見ないとしたら、帰れない
Well then.
じゃあ
Do I have to see it?
見ないといけないですか?
I see.
なるほど
cute.
可愛い
Well then, money.
じゃあ、お金と
Well, a little.
まあ、ちょっと
Hey, I'll see.
ね、見る
Oh, are you okay?
あ、大丈夫?
hey.
ね
This is a place where you can increase your supply.
増 やしてくれるとこですよね
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
うん、うん、うん
of course.
もちろん
a bit.
少し
It's a little.
少しです
Yeah.
うん
thank you.
ありがとう
Isn't it okay to take pictures?
撮っていいんじゃない?
Is it a video?
動画ですか?
No, just a little.
いや、ちょっとだけ
I'll delete it later.
あとで消します
no.
いや
erase.
消す
What should I do?
どうしよう
oh.
おお
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ、めっちゃキレイ
Wow,
うわ、
amazing.
すごい
touch?
触 る?
No, wait a minute, um.
いや、ちょっと、あの
No?
ダメ?
Well then, on your own.
じゃあさ、自分でさ
I made this face myself.
これさ、自分で おままの顔やったじゃん
This way, yes.
こっち、そう
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
By yourself.
自分で
Oh, that's so erotic.
あ、すっげーエロい
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
Have you ever done something like this?
こんなことしたことある?
Eh, amazing.
えー、すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Let's end this now.
もう、終わりにしましょう
It's over now.
もう、終わった
No, no, no, no, wait a minute.
いや、いや、いや、いや、ちょっと待ってよ
Because I haven't seen it yet.
まだ見てないから
It's over now.
もう、終わりました
I haven't seen it, I haven't seen it.
見てない、見てない
Let's end this now.
もう、終わりにしましょう
I'm going home too.
私も帰ります
That's it.
ここまでです
That's a bit cold.
それはちょっと冷たいじゃん
Okay, that's it.
いい じゃん、ここまで
Hey, you took it, didn't you?
ちょっと、取ったじゃないですか
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
It's okay to say it once.
1回言ってはいいでしょ
How much did you take?
どんだけ取った?
I'll go home when I'm done.
終わったら帰ります
what?
何?
No, no, I can't give it to you yet.
いや、いや、まだ 渡せないから
Because I haven't taken it yet.
まだ取ってないから
You took it, right?
取ったじゃないですか
Are you still going with Mantu?
まだ、マンツと行く?
You know each other, right?
知り合いじゃないですか
I'm off to go now.
もう、行きますね
No, I'm going home.
いや、帰るね
I'm going home.
帰るね
Not yet, not yet.
まだ、まだ
Because I took it.
取っちゃったから
I haven't deleted this yet, Data.
まだ、これ消してないよ、データ
You want to erase it, right?
消したいでしょ
that's right.
そうです
It won't go away, it'll stay like this.
消えないよ、このままじゃん
Is it okay?
いいの?
It's a waste.
もう、もったいない
This way.
このまんま
I've already taken everything.
もう、全部取ったけど
It's different to talk about it, isn't it?
話して違うじゃないですか
No, you're saying something different.
いや、話して違うこと言ってんじゃん
No, because it was already the first time.
いや、だってもう、最初だったよ
Make sure to take off your underwear too.
下着も脱ぐやつにして
Well, I'll just say that you'll have to pay for it and be satisfied with it.
それは、ほら、 お 金を出して納得するという 話でしてやる
Right?
んだ でしょ
He said he was good.
自分がいいって言ってた
So, take it already.
だから、もう、取って
I haven't taken it yet.
まだ、取ってないって話
Just a little bit.
もう、ちょっと
Since I took it, I said no.
取 った から、ダメって話で
I'm done with it now.
もう、 終わりにしました
As far as time goes, I haven't got it yet.
時間とかまで言って、まだ取れてないから、
I have to take a lot.
いっぱい取んなきゃいけない
Please judge that at your own discretion.
それは、勝手に判断してね
Please decide that.
それ を 決 めてください
That was a decision made by the two of you.
それは、2人で決めたことでしょ
I haven't decided yet.
決めてない
You said it yourself.
自分で言ったじゃん
I didn't say that.
言ってないです
You can take it.
取っていいんです
I'll give you the money.
お金渡すから
You want money, right?
お金欲しいでしょ
I want this.
これ、欲しいです
But I'm going home.
でも、私、帰ります
Well, I haven't taken it.
まあ、取ってない
Already this.
もう、これ
Because it's like this.
このままだから
I'll go out and take this home.
これ、出て持って帰る
This is different from a promise.
これは、約束と違うことです
Bring this data home.
これ、データ持って帰ってさ
That's not it.
それは、ないです
That's what I'm talking about.
そういう話をしてる
That's a decision.
それは、決策です
I am a PMA.
PMAとしてる
picture?
え?
You want to decide, right?
決したいでしょ
So, it's just a little bit...
だから、それは、もう、ちょっと、
Please step back.
下がってください
I'll finish in a moment.
ちょっと、終わります
It's over.
終わりです
Will it flow?
流します?
No.
ダメです
It is no good to flush it.
流すのは、ダメです
terrible.
やばい
No.
ダメです
da
ダ
This is me.
メ です
I don't like it.
嫌だ
want.
欲しい
Don't touch me.
触らないで
You didn't touch it, did you?
触ってないでしょ
I haven't touched it.
触ってない
You didn't touch it, did you?
触ってないでしょ
No.
ダ メです
I haven't touched it, so it's fine.
触ってないから、いいでしょ
No.
ダメです
delicious.
美味しい
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃ美味しい
It was really zoomed in.
なんか、めっちゃズームになってた
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
delicious.
美味しい
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
Dislike
嫌
is.
だ
It got on my face.
顔 についた
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
No.
ダメ
Stick out your tongue.
舌、出して
Take it out again.
もう一回、出して
Flow this.
流して、これ
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Listen.
聞いて
Take my hand.
手を引いて
He's sleeping.
寝てるじゃん
It's konji, isn't it?
こんじでしょ
sorry.
ごめんなさい
One more time.
もう一回
Guess it.
当てて
No more.
もうダメ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I don't like it.
嫌だ
No.
ダ メ
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理
No.
ダメ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Impossible.
無理
No.
ダメ
You're saying you don't like it.
嫌だって言ってるじゃん
That's different, isn't it?
それは違うでしょ
Not nearby.
近くない
That's different, isn't it?
それは違うでしょ
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理
I'm going home.
帰る
Read the police.
警察読む
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってよ
That's different, isn't it?
それは違うでしょ
It's not close.
近くないです
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Let's finish quickly.
早く終わろう
I don't like it.
嫌だ
If you listen to me, I'll be kind to you.
言 うこと聞いてくれたら 優しくするし
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Because it will end.
終 わるから
It would be better if it ended.
終 わるほうがいいでしょ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
What do you think?
どうだ?
It's ticklish.
くちくちってするわ
What is this?
何 これ?
Open.
開け
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It won't end.
終わんない
Because it won't end.
終わんないから
It's coming out.
出てきてる
end.
終わり
end?
終わり?
I want it to end.
終 わ り て いたい
Only myself.
自分だけ
Because it will end.
終わるから
I'll let it flow.
流すよ
You don't like it, do you?
嫌でしょ
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
It's better for it to end, right?
終わるほうがいいでしょ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You understand.
分かってんじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You already know.
もう分かるでしょ
What should I do?
どうしたらしようかな?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Please be kind.
優しくやってくれ
I'll finish it right away.
すぐ終わってあげるから
Do it properly.
ちゃんとやって
Because I'm not good at it.
下手だから
Do it comfortably.
気持ちよくやって
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Just squeeze it.
手しごいてちょうど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Just jerking off.
おしごいてちょうど
Look over here.
こっち見ながら見て
You're good at it.
上手じゃん
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
cry
泣いて
Ru.
る
Deeply.
深 く
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Can I wash it?
洗っていい?
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it hurts.
痛い
I felt so sick that I got excited.
気持ち悪すぎて 興奮しちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Do you think so?
思ってる?
That's right.
そりゃ
I'll give you the money properly.
ちゃんとお金渡すし
Felon
フェロン
on hand
上 手
Yes.
い ね
Who taught you this?
誰に教わったんだ?
I haven't been taught.
教わってないです
I learned it.
教わったじゃん
producer?
プロデューサー?
ERROR
フェロン好きっしょ
絶 対好きだよね
No.
ダメ
ERROR
もうここまで来た
No.
違うよ
ERROR
もう一緒にやる
That's fine.
いいじゃん
a little bit.
ちょっと
No, we're together.
いや、一緒じゃん
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Why not?
なんでダメなの?
ERROR
気持ち悪くないでしょ
でも一緒にやる
That's it.
だ ってそこは
Can I still go?
まだいけるの
Selling, selling, selling.
売れ売れ売れ
So, give me money.
だから、お金をね
Well, double that.
じゃあ、倍
I'll paste it twice.
倍貼りますよ
It's double that.
倍ですよ
Double this.
これの倍
Have a look?
見てみ?
Take a look inside.
中身見てみって
It's double this.
これの倍だよ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけで
Five or six minutes left.
あと 5、6分
Maybe two or three minutes.
2、3分かもしれない
It's a little nice, isn't it?
ちょっといいでしょ
Should I add that too?
そこも付けたらいい?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I put on rubber for the first time in a while.
ゴム久しぶりに付ける
If you put rubber on it, you won't know.
ゴム付けたら分かんないんだよ
I want to attach it.
付けたい
You get it.
分かるでしょ
picture?
え?
What do you think?
どうでしょ
Against it.
反対して
Should I put rubber on it?
ゴム付けたらいいの?
It's like this.
こんないよ
Really.
めっちゃ
め っちゃ
long time no see.
久しぶり
It's the top and bottom though.
上と下なんだけどさ
It's been a long time since I put it on.
めちゃめちゃ久しぶりに付けた
It's rolled up a little bit.
ちょまちょって巻いてる
It's fresh.
新鮮だわ
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すっごいね
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Idolman child.
アイドルマン子
I went out for a while.
ちょっと出てみた
A real man?
目大丈夫?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Look at me.
こっちを見て
Move.
動いて
Look with your mouth open.
口を開けて見て
It's going to move.
動いちゃう
Please move.
動いてくれ
I got used to it.
慣れた
Down, down.
下、下
Awesome.
すっごい
Move.
動いて
I added rubber.
ゴム付けた
Air point.
エアポイン
Move.
動いてよ
I added rubber.
ゴム付けた
Wouldn't it be nice to put some rubber on it?
ゴム付けたらいいでしょ?
I added rubber.
ゴム付けた
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Can I take it out?
出していい?
出していいのか?
what?
何?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry.
ごめんね
I haven't put it out.
出してないよ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
Because I haven't released it.
出してないからね